<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<ModMetaData>
  <name>Brain Implants and More (implants)!(Continued)</name>
  <author>jonny02 and explodoboy</author>
  <supportedVersions><li>1.6</li></supportedVersions>
  <packageId>hobbes77.MBI</packageId>
  <url></url>
  <description>
VERSION 3.0
REVISION 1

Brain Implants and More (implants)! adds new implants, mostly for the brain, but not just limited to that! :D

The implants have not one, not two, but THREE tiers, each one more powerful than the last!


The implants are as follows:

AI Chip: Acts like a Painstopper but with a boost to Consciousness, up to 250%!

Psychic Chip: Sensitivity to Psychic events are reduced, completely by tier 3.

Stomach Chip: Food Poisioning risk is reduced, completely by tier 3.

Toxic Chip: Toxic Buildup increases slower, its buildup stopped completely by tier 3.

Medical Chip: Tending speed and quality is increased, up to 125%. Surgery Success chance is also incrased, tier 3 making failiure nearly impossible.

Farmer Chip: Increases plant work speed, up to 275%!

Mining Chip: Increases mining speed, up to 275%!

Immuno Chip: Increases immunity gain speed, up to 225%! (Immuno chip has an additional Crude tier, which has a negative side-effect alongside it.)

Sleepstopper Chip: Removes the need for sleep entirely. (Only craftible with Glitterworld Chipset)

Information Chip: Skill gain is increased, up to 300%!

Research Chip: Research speed is increased, up to 300%!

Nanotech Chip: ALL wounds that damage limbs/organs will heal slowly without needing tending, but often outpacing bleeding except for the worst of wounds. Medical conditions are left untouched, however. (Only craftable with Glitterworld Chipset)


Chipsets are the foundation of this mod, to build these implants you need to buy Chipsets, which can only be obtained from orbital traders. The chipsets are:

Primitive Chipset (Tier 0)

Basic Chipset (Tier 1)

Advanced Chipset (Tier 2)

Glitterworld Chipset (Tier 3)

Chipsets aren't flammable, and tier 2+ don't deteriorate when outside as they're in sealed packages. They can, however, still be stolen by raiders. So, lock them securely.


You craft the implants and brains on the electric assembler, included in this mod. You unlock it by researching Brain Interfacing, which requires the Multi-Analyser to research.

More implants are constantly being made and rebalanced.

Thanks for downloading! Please, if you find anything wrong or unbalanced with the mod, please go to the Discussions and look for the Bugs and Suggestions pinned discussion, we are listening... Always listening... >:D
</description>
</ModMetaData>